state-of-the-art-mailer.com 2019-05-18

# SOTAM - Terms Of Service

## Privacy Policy 

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to http://state-of-the-art-mailer.com and http://bucketsofbanners.com and Brathe LLC and the Trade Name StateOfTheArtSites and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Brathe LLC or the Trade Name of StateOfTheArtSites will include http://state-of-the-art-mailer.com and http://bucketsofbanners.com. By using the StateOfTheArtSites websites, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. 

**_Collection of your Personal Information_**   
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through StateOfTheArtSites websites public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. 

We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future. 

**_Sharing Information with Third Parties_**  
StateOfTheArtSites does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. 

StateOfTheArtSites may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. StateOfTheArtSites may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to StateOfTheArtSites, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. 

StateOfTheArtSites may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on StateOfTheArtSites or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of StateOfTheArtSites; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of StateOfTheArtSites, or the public. 

**_Automatically Collected Information_**    
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by StateOfTheArtSites. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the StateOfTheArtSites websites. 

**_Links_**    
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. 

**_Security of your Personal Information_**    
StateOfTheArtSites secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. StateOfTheArtSites uses the following methods for this purpose: 

  * MD5 Encryption Algorithm

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed. 

**_Children Under Thirteen_**    
StateOfTheArtSites does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. 

**_E-mail Communications_**    
From time to time, StateOfTheArtSites may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication. 

If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from So Alive After 55, you may opt out of such communications by clicking on the UNSUBSCRIBE button located at the bottom of emails.. 

**_Changes to this Statement_**    
StateOfTheArtSites reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy. 

**_Contact Information_**   
StateOfTheArtSites welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that StateOfTheArtSites has not adhered to this Statement, please contact StateOfTheArtSites at: 

Brathe LLC c/o StateOfTheArtSites  
Attn: Brad Webb Owner/Operator   
2234 North Federal Hwy # 1096  
Boca Raton, Florida 33431   
Email Address: stateoftheartsites@gmail.com   
Telephone number:   
561-350-6519   
Effective as of March 31, 2008 

© 2010 & Beyond StateOfTheArtSites. All Rights Reserved.
